Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Sweet Secrets=
=أسرار حلوة=
=Episode 23= (Crimson Truth)
=الحلقة 23= (الحقيقة القرمزية)
You Zimei.
أنت زيمي.
When did you tell her I'd die because of the Mei pearl?
متى قلت لها أنني سأموت بسبب لؤلؤة مي؟
And when did you tell her to offer me the pearl?
ومتى قلت لها أن تقدم لي اللؤلؤة؟
Don't think that because you're the Supreme Priest of Wujian,
لا تظن أنه بسبب كونك الكاهن الأعلى في ووجيان،
I wouldn't dare touch you.
لا أجرؤ على لمسك.
If you dare to manipulate my wife again,
إذا تجرأت على التلاعب بزوجتي مرة أخرى،
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I lied to her.
لقد كذبت عليها.
I was selfish.
لقد كنت أنانيًا.
But I only wanted you to live.
ولكنني أردت فقط أن تعيش.
No one can stop my decision.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يوقف قراري.
This is yours.
هذه لك.
Take it back.
خذها مرة أخرى.
(After all these years of struggle,)
(بعد كل هذه السنوات من النضال)
(we were both just pawns in Father's game.)
(كنا مجرد بيادق في لعبة الأب.)
(The Chi and the Mei can never reunite,)
(لا يمكن للتشي والمي أن يجتمعا أبدًا)
(and Wujian is about to perish.)
(ووجيان على وشك الهلاك.)
(Brother,)
(أخ،)
(in the Prison of Beasts,)
(في سجن الوحوش)
(you took the blow meant for me,)
(لقد تلقيت الضربة التي كانت موجهة لي)
(I won't forget it.)
(لن أنسى ذلك.)
(Forgive me.)
(سامحني.)
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you don't have to live here anymore.
لا يتوجب عليك العيش هنا بعد الآن.
Mr. Jing.
السيد جينغ.
Are you driving me away?
هل أنت تبعدني عنك؟
What's the point of you staying here?
ما الهدف من بقائك هنا؟
It's alright.
لا بأس.
Let me stay by your side.
دعني أبقى بجانبك.
Wherever you go, I'll go.
أينما ذهبت سأذهب.
Whatever you need, I'll become that.
مهما كانت احتياجاتك، سأصبح ذلك.
As long as you let me stay.
طالما سمحت لي بالبقاء.
As long as I'm with you.
ما دمت معك.
You said
أنت قلت
you wouldn't abandon me.
لن تتخلى عني.
You didn't lie,
لم تكذب
did you?
هل فعلت؟
I'm just that fickle,
أنا متقلبة للغاية
and who are you pretending to be so pitiful for?
ومن تتظاهر بأنك مثير للشفقة هكذا؟
Pack your things and get out.
قم بجمع أغراضك واخرج.
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
Right.
يمين.
What is love worth anyway?
ما قيمة الحب على أية حال؟
Our fate has already been decided,
لقد تم تحديد مصيرنا بالفعل،
but in this life,
ولكن في هذه الحياة،
you shouldn't have to bear the pain again.
لا ينبغي عليك أن تتحمل الألم مرة أخرى.
Lanyue and I once defied the Wujian Rules,
لقد تحديت أنا ولانيوي قواعد ووجيان ذات مرة،
and fell in love.
ووقعت في الحب.
Father and Mother's union already brought shame upon Wujian.
لقد جلب اتحاد الأب والأم بالفعل العار على Wujian.
Father planted the Mei pearl within you and your sister,
لقد زرع الأب لؤلؤة المي بداخلك وأختك،
so that we could never love each other through lifetimes.
حتى لا نتمكن أبدًا من حب بعضنا البعض طوال حياتنا.
But in our past life, you died for me.
لكن في حياتنا الماضية، مت من أجلي.
I swore an oath,
لقد أقسمت اليمين،
never to betray you,
لن أخونك أبدًا،
to protect you forever.
لحمايتك إلى الأبد.
Wujian
وجيان
then sealed my memories.
ثم ختمت ذكرياتي.
Please, open your eyes and look at me.
من فضلك افتح عينيك وانظر إلي.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Please, just open your eyes and look at me once.
من فضلك افتح عينيك وانظر إلي مرة واحدة.
In the dream realm, the Mei pearl's light reawakened my memories.
في عالم الأحلام، أيقظ ضوء لؤلؤة مي ذكرياتي.
I knew then,
عرفت حينها
our fate continues in this life.
مصيرنا يستمر في هذه الحياة.
Lanyue,
لانيو,
I've finally found you.
لقد وجدتك أخيرا.
So,
لذا،
we're destined to love each other,
نحن مقدرون أن نحب بعضنا البعض،
yet destined to part again.
ولكن من المقرر أن ينفصلا مرة أخرى.
Aren't we?
أليس كذلك؟
That's the very rule I intend to change.
هذه هي القاعدة التي أعتزم تغييرها.
A thousand years ago, you took a blade for me.
منذ ألف عام، أخذت شفرة من أجلي.
I won't let you suffer the same fate.
لن أسمح لك أن تعاني نفس المصير.
Lu Huayan,
لو هوايان,
if you die,
إذا مت
I'll never live alone again.
لن أعيش بمفردي مرة أخرى.
Li Motong,
لي موتونج,
whether I'm Lanyue
هل أنا لانيو؟
or Lu Huayan,
أو لو هوايان،
whatever the rules or fate,
مهما كانت القواعد أو المصير،
I've made my choice.
لقد اتخذت قراري.
Even if the heavens fall,
حتى لو سقطت السماوات،
I'll still go forward,
سأستمر في المضي قدما،
to be with you.
أن أكون معك.
(What must come,)
(ما يجب أن يأتي)
(will come eventually.)
(سوف يأتي في نهاية المطاف.)
(The mortal realm will soon fall into chaos.)
(سوف يقع عالم البشر في حالة من الفوضى قريبًا.)
The Gate of Wujian is about to collapse.
بوابة ووجيان على وشك الانهيار.
Wujian's fate hangs by a thread.
مصير ووجيان معلق بخيط.
I must return to Wujian
يجب أن أعود إلى ووجيان
to save it.
لحفظه.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
The Mei pearl is within me.
لؤلؤة مي موجودة في داخلي.
Wujian's fate is tied to mine as well.
مصير Wujian مرتبط بمصيري أيضًا.
Take me back.
أعدني.
Let's face it together.
دعونا نواجه الأمر معًا.
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪